In my experience, once you talk to
people, they usually open up pretty
quickly.
People are always telling me that I seem
intimidating.
I'm not very good at approaching
people on my own.
Nice to find someone who shares
my love of manga!
I had always been kinda bored
here since I hadn't found others I had
much in common with.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- No problem.
What if the only reason someone felt
alone was because no one had found…
The right key?
- HAMBURGER BOM BOM
- And then that guy was like…
Hey, Amamiya, are you even listening?
Hm? Yeah, course I am!
No, I'm not.
THE RAMPARTS OF ICE
EPISODE 2 LOCKSMITH
Now come on, let's go have some fun.
I'm not going anywhere!
Oh, what should I do?
And frustrated.
- And pissed off.
- Come on.
- It'll be super fun!
- I told you…
I'm not going anywhere!
Leave me alone.
Seriously.
Bye.
Sorry. Are you okay?
Oh! I knew it! It was you.
Mr. Giraffe.
Sorry I ignored you, but I couldn't see
you.
Oh, um, well…
- Hm?
- Please pretend to be my friend.
I'm sorry.
Please just stay with me until these
two guys leave me alone.
Huh?
SWIFT
Okay, well, I found my friend, so
I'm fine now. Bye.
Huh? What? What? Huh?
BLURRY
Does she know these guys?
- Stare…
- I guess not.
HURRY
High schoolers these days are such
freaks.
Right?
Thank you very much.
Huh? But I didn't do anything, did I?
Wait, didn't you know them?
They came up and started talking to me.
Wow, you're so popular!
It's not like that!
Uh. Or at least, um, I mean, back there…
This wasn't like that.
They were the kind of guys who only cared
about their own enjoyment, not mine.
They talked down to me.
I-I'm not interested in guys like that.
Or…
Oh.
Agh, why am I blabbering at him
like this?
Oh man, I'm totally oversharing.
I'm gonna weird him out.
Hmm.
So wait, are you saying I should've
knocked their lights out?
What?
Oh, n-n-no, you don't have to go
that far.
Are you sure?
And I'm sorry.
I feel bad.
I kind of used you to get away from them.
Huh? What? Why? It's totally fine.
That's not the kind of thing that
would upset me.
You're good.
Do you live around here, Himuro?
No, I was heading to the community
center.
Huh? Hey, that's where I'm going!
Do you wanna walk there together?
Mm-hm.
Since there are no club activities
during the exam preparation period, your
daily routine tends to get disrupted.
Oh, homeroom is going way over!
Koyun, I'm so sorry to keep you waiting!
Set up a study schedule.
So… uh…
Hm?
Can you, uh, tell me your name, please?
Oh, right. I guess I never actually
introduced myself, did I?
Sorry about that.
Yota. Just call me Yota.
I can't just call him by his first name!
Nice to meet you, Himuro.
Oh. Well, um…
My name… isn't Himuro, it's Hikawa.
What? I'm so sorry!
I wish you would've told me sooner.
So… how far are we from the community
center?
I'm directionally challenged.
About five more minutes and we're there.
Five minutes.
Can we keep this conversation going?
So, Hikawa… Are you and Miki close?
Oh. Well, um…
We're old friends.
We went to the same elementary and
middle schools.
Huh. That's really cool.
Uh.
Since junior high…
So does that mean he's seen what she's
really like, then?
Modern Miki!
You know, to be honest, I thought Miki
was way better the way she used to be!
I think so too.
Oh, good.
It bugs me.
I wanna shout it from the rooftops.
It just feels like such a waste, y'know?
Mm.
- [Cracking up} Hold up.
- HAMBURGER BOM BOM
Seriously?
Wait, is that Yota?
Hm?
Oh yeah, you're right.
No way… The girl next to him is…
Huh?
MEITEN COMMUNITY CENTER
Uh.
- Shh.
Here, we saved you a seat.
Oh. Thanks.
But I don't understand.
What're you both doing here together?
- Together?
- Good question.
Well?
Still waiting for an answer.
Quiet.
Uh. What're you…
Oh! I'm so sorry.
This came out of nowhere!
You guys should've warned me beforehand
instead of just springing it on me like
- that!
- I actually told her not to text you.
So then it'd be a surprise.
Really, Koyun?
Can't believe you played along with him!
Anyway, did you punch the guys who
were messing with her?
- Did you knock their lights out?
- No.
Hikawa said I didn't have to.
I told him it really wasn't necessary.
Lame!
Are you two taking the same train?
I'll walk you to the station.
Aw, thank you!
Yota, do you always go to that
study room?
Uh, yeah, actually.
My younger brother and sister are
still little, so it can get pretty
noisy at home.
Mmm-hmm! What age?
Oh, my brother and sister are both
three years old.
- They're fraternal twins.
- Wow, that's quite an age gap.
So, part of it's to get away from the
noise at home, but, in general, I just
- concentrate way better at the center.
- Oh, I get that.
I didn't scroll on my phone even one
time.
I'm very proud of myself.
That's not that hard.
- Oh.
- Huh?
Hold on a sec.
All that studying…
Gotta replenish my energy with
some sugar.
Ooh, good idea!
I think I'll get one too.
He's taller than the vending machine.
Must be nice.
I wish I had been born that tall.
Go ahead, pick what you want.
Oh, are you sure?
Sweet red bean soup, right?
You know me so well!
This was nice of you, Yota.
I'll make sure to get yours the
next time.
Whoa! Ah, what happened?!
Whoa! Oh! Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay…
FLUSTER
Why'd you have a zillion coins instead of
just using bills?!
- I know, sorry.
- Oh, jeez.
NATURAL SPARKLING LEMON WATER
REFRESHING AND DELICIOUS APPLE JUICE
- Want a drink?
- Huh?
- What about you, Hikawa?
- Me?
Oh, no, uh, I- I…
- Hm.
Well, Miki will just have to pick
for you.
You got it.
COCOA, SWEET RED BEAN SOUP,
AMAZAKE CORN POTAGE
But I want the sweet red bean soup,
so she'll get the sweet red
Hmm, I think she wants the corn
potage soup.
But I want the sweet red bean soup,
so she'll get the sweet red
Seriously?
Well, I want us to drink the
same thing so we can talk about how
delicious it is!
So self-centered.
They seem so close.
I know I mentioned this earlier, but
we went to the same cram school back
in junior high.
So me, Miki, and Minato used to hang out
all the time.
Yup. After cram school, we'd always get
something to eat and just talk.
Mina-
Oh, wait, you're talking about Amamiya?
Whoa! Koyun, I had no idea you knew him!
Well, I wouldn't say I know him.
STRETCH
Oh no, was he bullying you again?
Again?
Uh, well, no, he…
I'm sorry about him.
I swear, you can just ignore him.
What?
Have you and Amamiya had a falling out
or something?
No, I'm just kidding.
Koyun, Yota, and Minato…
So, tell me, Hikawa, does everybody
around you call you Koyun?
- Mm?
- Koyun!
- Uh, yes?
- It's a pretty good nickname!
- Yeah, right?
- Don't let it get to your head.
I know I said it before, but just call me
Yota.
I don't like to make things super
complicated.
Or too formal.
- Uh…
- Oh, I feel you.
I prefer Miki to some dumb little
nickname.
Hmm, is that so?
Thanks again, Yota!
Hey! See you tomorrow?
Yep, I'll be there.
Okay, have a great night.
Yeah, see ya!
See ya tomorrow.
Hmm
Koyuki…
Hikawa…
Has she… always gone here?
I think her last name's Hikawa.
She's in class two.
I heard she's a loner, and super
unfriendly.
Class two was the quiet class, if I
remember correctly.
Maybe she just hasn't found anyone
else that she vibes with yet.
I'd always been curious about her
whenever I saw her.
She's alone again.
SQUISH
Every time I see her…
I feel…
Sorry for- Hm?
INCOMING CALL
Hey, Minato. Sorry, but can we meet up?
I wanna talk about something.
Yeah. No problem.
So, what do you wanna talk about?
Aren't you cold?
I wanna break up.
What makes you say that?
I can't trust you.
I mean, look, you're a very nice
guy, I'll give you that, but…
I don't think…
I don't think you ever really liked me,
did you, Minato?
Your heart was never really in it.
Did I do something wrong to make you
feel that way?
Stop responding to everything with a
question.
You always do that.
Just show me how you really feel
for once!
Know what I think?
You don't have a real sense of self.
I'm home.
Wait, what were you doing out this late?
Is something the matter?
Mm? Nah, don't worry.
It's nothing important.
Yay!
I mean, shoot, oh no, that really sucks,
buddy!
I just got dumped. Can you at least
pretend to feel bad for me or something?
How many times is this now?
Yeah, at this point it's actually kind of
funny.
But I'm sure you'll find another
girlfriend soon.
What? Did you get dumped again, Amamiya?
That's right.
I was in the middle of studying last
night, and she called and asked me to
- come meet her. Then dumped me.
- Oof, brutal.
I always get dumped, and I just
keep asking myself…
- How come?
- Huh?
Well, I, uh…
HE DOES THIS IF I DON'T KEEP AN EYE ON HIM
- Ugh.
- Fujita, don't let him charm you like
that! You can't look this guy in the eye
for more than three seconds!
BA-DUMP, BA-DUMP
- I'll hold him off. Run while you still
- Morning, everyone!
- Can!
- What the…
Seriously, Minato?
What have you done this time?
- Jeez.
- I didn't do anything.
Why do you assume that every time?
Oh. That's right.
Hm…
I'm telling you, the school store's
a treasure trove if you go early.
- Hey, Yota.
- Hm?
Did I happen to see you walking
Hikawa home yesterday?
I know what he'll say…
Huh? No way, you've got it all wrong.
It's not like that.
- Oh, you saw us.
- Huh?
Hm?
We just happened to run into each other,
so we walked together.
Oh, okay. So that's all?
Just saying, 'cause you kinda…
SCHOOL NURSE'S OFFICE
Oh.
Hey, Hikawa!
Why are you in the nurse's office?
- Are you sick or hurt of something?
- Um.
No, I just, I, um…
Huh? Hey, what is it?
Oh, Yota, hi.
First name basis?
Hey there, Koyun!
Him too?
Not feeling that well?
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
I'm just here to get close to the heater.
But why's that? Do you think it's
that cold out today?
You seen the weather? It's freezing.
Got your contacts in?
Jeez, it's like I don't even exist.
- Yeah! I can see perfectly.
- Oh, good.
Hey, Miss Hikawa.
Oh!
You're letting all of the precious heat
out.
So, if you're going, would you close the
door?
Go on, shoo!
She got pretty mad at you there.
Noriko is always like that.
Hikawa, you going to the fourth floor?
We're going upstairs too.
Well, I…
Gotta go to the first floor to, um…
my locker.
My locker.
Gotcha.
BRISKLY
- Well then, I'll just, uh…
- See ya in a bit!
In a bit?
Did they really "just happen" to run into
each other?
Woo! I studied my butt off today!
Then again, I always do.
But to be honest, there're things I
still don't get, and sometimes I
wanna talk things out and ask questions
while we're studying.
Then after school tomorrow, wanna just
study in the classroom?
I can help explain stuff.
You're cool with that?
Please! Share all your wisdom and smarts
with me, Sensei!
Well, I don't know about all that.
BAM
Sensei! Oh no!
Owie.
Uh…
Jeez, that looks like it hurt. You
alright?
Eh, I bump my head into things all
the time.
- Oh.
- Oy, Yota's class…
Seems like it'll be noisy.
- Hm.
- Don't worry.
Huh?
When the bell rings, the noisy ones all
leave.
Yeah, they all go home.
He just read my mind.
I KIND OF LIKE IT
Noise isn't really Koyun's vibe.
How embarrassing.
SPACE FOR ONE PERSON
Huh.
Let's play for it.
- Rock, paper, sci-
- Oh!
- Go ahead, Sir!
No, please sit.
- I insist.
- No, it's okay. Take it.
- PR face.
- We're getting off at the next station.
What?
Please use the stairs in the middle of
the platform to transfer to other lines.
- Oh no! Hurry! Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no,
- The doors on platform three are closing.
Oh no!
HUFF, HUFF
- You could've just let him have it.
- I dunno, it just came out.
Why did you have to lie to the man?!
I was embarrassed!
FOGGY
Speaking of embarrassing, my heavy
breathing's fogged up the window.
Oh no, you're making me laugh too!
After finals, I'm back to working after
school, which means we won't be able to
THEY TEND TO TALK A LITTLE MORE WHEN
walk home together. walk home together.
THEY ARE ABOUT TO SAY GOODBYE
- Huh?
- You've never been right?
I'll throw in a free smile for ya!
Hmm.
- Stylish burger! Yay!
- Honestly, I'm a bit intimidated
by the idea of going there alone.
BECAUSE I'M ONLY A HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
Their burgers are crazy expensive.
If I ask the manager, he might give you a
discount!
Sure, I'll knock some Yen off for ya.
SHOP MANAGER
If you're scared to go alone, you can
just drag Yota along?
Mm.
Wait, no, Yota has his after school club.
Hm.
Well, see ya later!
- ROOM 201 HIKAWA
- See you later.
Oh.
The laundry.
- Hm?
- Was I… smiling just now?
Wait.
I feel a lingering happiness from today,
and I'm actually looking forward to
tomorrow.
It's easier to be alone.
I'm having fun.
I don't want to get attached.
I wanna see them again.
I want to be left alone.
I'm excited for tomorrow.
I feel all of these feelings… and all
so deeply.
But they conflict.
So then… what is it I really want?
I have no idea what I'm feeling.
GRADE 1 CLASS 6
- Did you get the homework at all? I was
- Sneak peak.
Completely lost. I literally had to ask
my sister to explain it to me.
Glad you made it.
- Ha, yeah I know. I was so embarrassed,
- Hi. Good morning.
She'll never let me live it down.
Miki just said she's running behind.
Oh, she texted me about it too.
Class five's homeroom tends to run long.
Hey, why don't I just create a new group
chat for us?
Oh. Smart.
- Wow.
- Oh, Minato. What's up?
So are you two…
Like, an item?
Huh? What? No!
We're not! No!
Miki's gonna be joining us here soon.
Miki too?
That's such a random group.
CLATTER
Huh? W- wait, Minato?!
Do you not want me to be here or
something?
No, it's not that at all.
Miki's acting more like herself.
So… are you all studying together?
That's right, you got it!
I see.
Sounds fun.
Let's get to it!
Huh?